Finding aid for Library (University of Michigan) Clipping file, ca. 1920-1980
Bentley Historical Library
- University of Michigan
  - R
    - Research.
      - February 1968-Marchv, 1971 (Box 48)
      - March 1971- (Box 48)
    - Research -- DNA Controversy (Box 48)
    - Research (by non-university firms located on North Campus).
      (see: North Campus-Research...)
    - Research Center for Group Dynamics.
      (see: Institute for Social Research-Research Center for Group Dynamics.)
    - Research Club of' Language Learning.
      (see: English Language Institute.)
    - Research Income Fund.
      (Set up by-W.W. Cook and the Michigan legislature. see: Law School-W.W. Cook Foundation; Law School-Legal Research.)
    - Reserve Officers Training Corps.
    - Residence Halls.
      (see: Housing; Dorms (Men); Dorms (Women); Dorms (General); List of residence halls for men and women in preface of the current Student Directory.)
    - Residential College Plan.
      (see: Literary College-Residential College.)
    - Residential College Players.
      (see: Dramatics-Student Groups. Residential Education Program. see: Education, School of)
    - "Resistance".
      (see: Peace Movements (An outgrowth of Student Peace UnionT7)
    - Respirator Center (polio).
    - Retirement plans.
      (see: Annuities.)
    - Rhetoric, Dept. of.
    - Rho Chi. Pharmaceutical Honorary Fraternity.
    - Rhodes Scholarships.
      (see: Fellowships.)
    - Richard, Father Gabriel.
      (see: Bibliography.)
    - Riding. (Box 48)
      (Includes University Woman's Riding Club, Crop and Saddle (women), Boots and Spurs (men), Pegasus Riding Club (1929-31).)
    - Rifle Teams and Club. (Box 48)
    - (Frances) Riggs Fellowships. England and U.S.
      (see: Foreign Students-Scholarships and Exchange.)
    - Ring.
      (see: Symbols.)
    - Riots (student).
      (see: Student Life; Radicals.)
    - Rochdale House.
    - Rocket Research.
      (see: Space Research.)
    - Rockford Players.
      (see: Dramatics-Rockford Players, etc.)
    - Roger Williams Guild.
      (see: Religion-Churches-Baptist.)
    - Rogers doors.
      (see: Museum of Art.)
    - Romance Language Journal Club. also called Romance Club.
    - Romance Languages and Literatures, Dept. of. (Box 48)
      (Includes French, Spanish, Italian, Portuguese, linguistics, see also: Societies-Foreign Languages.)
    - Roosevelt for King.
      (see: Political Clubs-Republicans.)
    - Rose Bowl 1969.
      (see: Football.)
    - Rosenthal (Bernard 1936). Kinetic Cube.
      (see: Memorials. (Not a memorial, however.))
    - ROTC (Reserve Officers Training Corp). (Box 46)
      (Includes Dept. of Military Science and Tactics. see also: Societies-Military; World War II-Army and Navy Education programs; Military Affairs, Office of (selective service); Ann Arbor-Defense (for local non-univ. units and Armed Forces Day). Activism (for ROTC protests).)
    - Rules and Regulations.
      (see: Dean-Men; Dean-Women (for material to 1962); Student Affairs, Office of (1962-Women's Joint Judiciary (Late hour infractions of dorm rules); Joint Judiciary Council (Student infractions); Students, Automobiles (Driving rules, infractions); Student Government-Board of Review; Student Affairs Committee, 192155 (Control Student Govt.).)
      - Round Table Club.
    - Rural Life and Education Institutes
    - Rural Health Conferences.
    - Rushing.
      (see: Sororities-Rushing; Fraternities-Rushing; Student Government.)
    - Russel (Henry) Award and Lecture. (Box 48)
    - Ruthven, Alexander G. (Pres.)-bibliography;-1939 Anniversary Dinner
      (see also: World War II-Administration policy.)
      - 1920-1929 (Box 48)
      - 1930 (Box 48)
      - 1931-1933 (Box 48)
      - 1934-1939 (Box 48)
      - 1940-1944 (Box 48)
      - 1945-1950 (Box 48)
      - 1951-1955 (Box 48)
      - 1956- (Box 48)
      - Anniversary Dinner, 1939 (Box 48)
  - S
    - Safety Committee.
      (see: University Safety Committee.)
    - Safety Education: University Safety Committee (Box 48)
      (Includes National Institute for Traffic Safety trainikng, Summer 1938)
    - Saginaw Forest.
      (Before 1950 see: Forestry. After 1950 see: Natural Resources, School of)
    - Sailing. (Box 49)
      (Includes Sailing Club, speedboats.)
    - Saint Mary's Student Chapel.
      (see: Religion-Churches-Catholic.)
    - Salaries.
      (see: (Faculty)-Faculty; Finances (legislative action))
    - Salvation Army.
    - Sanitation.
      (see: Public Health, School of.)
    - Selby Discussional
      (Formerly called Ann Arbor Discussional. see: Institute of Industrial Health.)
    - Scabbard and Blade.
    - Scalp and Blade (Buffalo and Erie Co. students).
      (see: Societies-Q-2.)
    - Scandinavian Club.
      (see: Foreign Students-Societies-Europe.)
    - Scandinavian Language.
      (see: Germanic Language and Literature, Dept. of)
    - Schizophrenia.
      (Research Center for the study of schizophrenia set up by Michigan State Hospital, Ypsilanti., U. of M., etc. .1958-). see Mental Health Research Institute.)
    - Scholarship.
      (see also: Freshmen; Michigan Society of Fellows)
      - 1921-1935 (Box 49)
      - 1936- (Box 49)
    - Scholarships --clippings
      (Includes fellowships prizes, and loans too. see also: Fellowships; Faculty Awards and Fellowships; Prizes; Hopwood Awards; Loan Funds; Foreign Students-Scholarships and Exchange; Finance-Trust Funds; World War II-War Bonds (Bomber Scholarship))
      - 1920-1932 (Box 49)
      - 1932-1937 (Box 49)
      - 1938-1943 (Box 49)
      - 1944-1947 (Box 49)
      - 1947-1949 (Box 49)
      - 1950-1952 (Box 49)
      - 1953-1955 (Box 49)
      - 1956-1963 (Box 49)
      - 1964- (Box 49)
    - Science. (Box 49)
      (Includes only general items; Natural Science Bldg. and Exhibits. see also: specific depts.; Institute of Science and Tech.; Summer Session-Campus Events (1946).)
    - Science Research Club.
    - Scientific Club.
    - Scroll.
      (see: Societies-Scroll.)
    - Sculpture.
      (see: Fine Arts, Dept. of; Architecture and Design, College of; Faculty-Fairbanks, Award.)
    - Sea Grant Colleges Program.
      (see: Great Lakes Research.)
    - Seal.
    - Security Officer.
      (see: Buildings and Grounds. see also: Crime; Students, Autos)
    - (John) Seeley Fellowships.
    - Seismograph Station.
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures, Dept. of 1952- (Box 49)
    - Selective Service Certification.
      (see: Military Affairs, Office of; Ann Arbor-Defense (local non-university. units).; Conscription,-(general file).)
    - Selective Service Counselor.
    - Seleucia Expedition.
      (See: Near Eastern Studies -- Mesopotamia Expedition)
    - Seminars.
      (see: under department or institute sponsoring the seminar.)
    - Senate,., 1922-1954 (Box 49)
      (Faculty-see: Senate (Faculty); tudent-see: Student Senate; Women-see: Women's League)
    - Senate (Faculty).
      (Minutes and Reports are in the Mich. Hist. Collection to 1948-. Afterwards in the office of the Sec. Sec., 1957-Dr. George McEwen, Eng. English Dept.)
      - 1959-1967
      - 1968-June 1970
      - 1970-January 1972
      - January 1971-
    - Senior Ball 1870- (Box 49)
      (Victory Ball was substituted for J-Hop and Senior Ball during WWII. see: Social Events.)
    - Senior Board (Cabinet).
      (see: Seniors.)
    - Senior Girls' Play (1903-30). (Box 49)
      (Included Senior Breakfast. Now changed to Senior Night. for which see: Junior Girls' Play.)
    - Senior Night.
      (see: Junior Girls' Play.)
    - Senior Society.
      (see: Societies-Senior Society.)
    - Seniors. (Box 49)
      (Includes Senior Board (Senior Cabinet), elections and officers, gift to the university, gifts to seniors, special tests, etc.; see also: Senior-Ball; Seniors-Traditions; Commencement;)
    - Seniors-Traditions. (Box 49)
      (Includes Swingout, Senior Canes and Cane Day, Senior Sing, Senior Banquet (for women's banquet see: Senior Girls' Play), Class Day. see also: Commencement; Junior Girls' Play; Senior Girls' Play; Senior Ball; Lantern Night.)
    - Service Awards.
      (For employee service awards see: Employees.)
    - Service Enterprises. (Box 49)
      (Includes Bindery, Mailing Service, Rental Properties Office, Photographic Services. For other branches see also: Buildings and Grounds (Plant Dept. and Instrument Shops); Food Service Building; Publications (printing); Alumni-Relations (Alumni Catalog Office): Students, Automobiles (parking).)
    - Sesquicentennial.
      (see: History-Sesquicentennial.)
    - Sesquigras.
    - Seventh Day Adventists.
    - Slide Rule Ball.
    - Shady Trails Camp (Northport).
      (see: Institute for Human Adjustment-Speech Clinic)
    - Shepard Lecture in Experimental Psychology.
    - Sigma Alpha Eta (Professional speech correction fraternity)
      (see: Societies-Debating and Oratorical (1950-))
    - Sigma Alpha Iota.
      (see: Societies-Sigma Alpha Iota)
    - Sigma Delta Chi. National honorary journalism fret. (Box 49)
    - Sigma Delta Phi (National honorary forensic society for women).
      (see: Societies-Debating and Oratorical .(1920-50).)
    - Sigma Delta Pi. Spanish Honor Society.
      (see: Societies-Foreign Language.)
    - Sigma Delta Psi (National Honorary Athletic Frat.).
    - Sigma Gamma Epsilon.
    - Sigma Rho Tau.
      (see: Societies-Sigma Rho Tau.)
    - Sigma Sigma Phi. (Chinese women's sorority).
      (see: Foreign Students-Societies-Asia.)
    - Sigma Xi.
      (see: Societies-Sigma Xi.)
    - Thomas Henry Simpson Memorial Institute for Medical Research 1927-(A branch of the Dept. of Internal Medicine,. Medical School). (Box 49)
    - Signs on Campus.
      (see: Societies-Alpha Phi Omega.)
    - Sings, concerts, etc
      (see: Bands; Music (for non-traditional sings); Traditions (for senior sing, Christmas sing, all-campus sing, etc.).)
    - Skating.
      (see: Hockey and Skating.)
    - Skiing. (Box 49)
      (Includes Ullr Ski Club.)
    - Skit Night.
      (see: Spring Weekend.)
    - Slavic Club.
    - Smitty's Coffeehouse.
      (see: Dormitories (General).)
    - Soaring Club.
    - Soccer, Speedball, etc.
      (see: Athletics-Intramural; Athletics-Intramural-Women.)
    - Social Implications of Modern Science.
      (see: Summer Session-Campus Events.)
    - Social Organization, Center for Research on.
    - Social Psychology, Degree in.
    - Social Science, Division of. (Box 49)
      (see also: Curriculum)
    - Social Science Research Project.
      (see: Institute for Human Adjustment-Social Science Research Projects.)
    - Social Security.
      (see: Summer Session-Campus Events (1950) for "social Security, Quest for" lectures)
    - Social Work, School of.
      - 1936-45
        (see: Institute of Public and Social Administration)
      - 1945--Established as the Social Work Institute and changed in 1951 to School of Social Work.
    - Social Work Club.
      (see: Social Work, School of.)
    - Social Work Institute.
    - Socialist Club.
      (see: Political Clubs-Socialist.)
    - Socieded Hispanics.
      (see: Societies-La Sociedad Hispanics.)
    - Societies- (general)
      (For misc. clubs see alphabetical arrangement which follows.-For, specific group look under name of the society, topic (i.e. Societies-Law), or department concerned (i.e., Psychology-for Psychology Club).)
      - General (Box 49)
      - A to F (Box 50)
        (Includes Alpha Xi Beta, Americans Committed to World, Responsibility, Beacon Club, Beta Iota Chi; Beta Sigma, Phi Bohemian Club, Boosters Club, Barnaby Club, Cleveland Club, Chess Club, Crest Club, Dance Club, Friars Club, Foreign Relations Club, Folklore Society)
      - G to P (Box 50)
      - Q to Z (Box 50)
    - Societies-Aeronautical, 2 folders (Box 50)
      (see also: Aviation)
    - Societies-Alpha Lambda Delta (freshmen women's honorary). (Box 50)
    - Societies-Foreign Language. (Box 50)
      (see also: Il Circolo Italiano; Le Cercle Francais; Socieded Hispanics; Deutscher Verein)
    - Societies-Alpha Phi Omega (Service Fret.). (Box 50)
    - Societies Architecture and Art, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Societies-Association of University of Michigan Scientists 1945- (Box 50)
    - Societies-Barristers. Law School. Senior Honorary. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Business Administration. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Case Clubs.
    - Societies-Chemistry. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Circle. Honorary for Assembly Association (Box 50)
    - Societies-Coif, Order of. Honor Society (top 10% of Law School) (Box 50)
      (see also: Law School (for honor's banquet))
    - Societies-Culture Club. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Debating and Oratorical (Box 50)
      (see also: Societies-Zeta Phi Eta)
    - Societies-Dentistry. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Deutscher Verein. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Druids (senior men's honor society). (Box 50)
    - Societies-Education. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Engineering, 3 folders (Box 50)
      (Includes: Transportation Club; Eta Kappa Nu; Pi Tau Sigma; Iota Alpha; Chi Epsilon; Alpha Tau Sigma; Web and Flange; Quarterdeck; Founderyman's Association.; Spoofuncup Award; Society of Automotive Engineers; Mechanical Engineer's Club; Michigan Metallurgical Society; Alpha Pi Mu; Society of Engineer's Wives; American Society of Civil Engineers; American Society of Tool Engineers; American Society of Engineering Education; American Society of Mechanical Engineers; American Society of Women Engineers; American Institute of Mining and Metal Engineers. see also: Societies-Triangles; Vulcans; Tau Beta Pi; Sigma Rho Tau.)
    - Societies-Faculty. (Box 50)
      (see also: Societies-Faculty Women's Club; Societies-Research Club.)
    - Societies-Faculty Women's Club. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Le Circle Francais., 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Societies-Foreign Students.
      (see: Foreign Students-Societies' (cards).)
    - Societies-Freshmen. (Box 50)
      (see: Societies-Phi Eta Sigma (men). Societies-Alpha Lambda Delta (women))
    - Societies-Galens. Medical Society. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Hillel,., 1926-1975; 5 folders (Box 50)
    - Societies-Honor-(general) (Box 50)
      (see also: Societies-Phi Beta Kappa; Societies-Phi Kappa Phi. For individual honoraries see cards following for division by men, women, and by type)
    - Societies-Honor (Men).
      (see: Societies-Honor (misc.); Societies-Druids (senior men);-Michigamua (seniors); Societies-Phi Eta Sigma (freshmen) Societies-Sphinx (juniors); Societies-Quadrants (independents) Societies-Hectorians (frat. men).)
    - Societies-Honor (Women) (1957)
      (see: Societies-Honor (misc.); Societies-Scroll (Sorority Seniors); Societies -Senior Society (independent seniors); Societies-Wyvern (junior women); Societies-Mortarboard (national senior women's honorary); Societies-Alpha 1-,embda Delta (freshmen); Societies-Circle (honorary for Assembly).)
    - Honor Societies (By Type) LIST, 1957
      (see: title or department. Alpha Lambda Delta (Fr. W.);-Alpha Omega Alpha (Med.); Arnold Air Society (USAF); Beta Gamma Slums (BA); Chi Epsilon (Civil Eng.); Delta Omega (Pub. Health); Delta Sigma Pi (BA); Eta Kappa Nu (Elect. Eng); Gamma Alpha (Grad. Sc.); Kappa Kappa Psi (Band); Omicron Kappa Upsilon (Dent.); Order of Coif (Law); Pershing Rifles (ROTC); Phi Chi Theta (BA); Phi Eta Sigma (Fr. M.); Phi Lambda Upsilon (Chem.); Phi Sigma Alpha (Pol. Sc.); Phi Sigma Society (Bio.); Pi Kappa Lambda (Music); Pi Tau Sigma (Mech. Eng.); Rho Chi (Pharm.); Scabbard and Blade (ROTC); Sigma Delta Pi (Span); Sigma Gamma Epsilon (Geo.); Sigma Xi (Science Res.); Tau Beta Phi (Eng.); Tau Beta Sigma (Band); Tau Sigma Delta (Arch).)
    - Societies-Ii Circolo Italiano. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Independents. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Inter-Arts Union. (Box 50)
    - Societies-International.
      (see: Political Clubs-International Relations; National Student Association (for International Student Association))
    - Societies-La Sociedad Hispanics. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Law Discussion Club. Early form of Case Clubs.
    - Societies-Law School. (Box 50)
      (see also: Societies-Michigan Crib; Societies-Student Bar Association; Societies-Barristers; Societies-Coif, Order of (Honorary))
    - Societies-Literary.
    - Societies (Locality)
      (see: under the appropriate alphabetical heading, see also; Foreign Students)
      - Societies (general)
      - Cleveland Club
      - Grindstone City, Mich.
      - Hawaii
      - Hiawatha (U.P.)
      - Harvard
      - Ispeming (U.P.)
      - Metropolitan Club (NYC and NJ)
      - Scalp and Blade (Buffalo and Erie Co.)
      - Southerners Club
      - Texas Club
      - Toledo Club.
    - Societies-Medical School. (Box 50)
      (see also: Societies-Galens)
    - Societies-Michigamua (senior men's honor society).
    - Box 50Societies-Michigan Crib. Pre-law society. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Michigan Dames 1914-. Originally called Association of Student's Wives. (Box 50)
    - Societies-Military. (Box 50)
      (see also: R.O.T.C.)
    - Societies-Mortar Board (national senior women's honorary) (Box 51)
    - Societies-Mu Phi Epsilon. Professional Music Sorority. (Box 51)
    - Societies-Music. (Box 51)
      (see also: Societies-Mu Phi Epsilon; Sigma Alpha Iota; Music (Band))
    - Societies-Music (Band). (Box 51)
      (Includes Kappa Kappa Psi (Men); Tau Beta Sigma (Women).)
    - Societies-Outing. (Box 51)
      (Includes Les Voyageurs, Town and Country Club, Graduate Outing Club, Outdoor Club, Hosteling Club.)
    - Societies-Phi Beta Kappa. (Box 51)
    - Societies-Phi Eta Sigma (freshmen men's honor society). (Box 51)
    - Societies-Phi Kappa Phi. (Box 51)
    - Societies-Political.
      (see: Political Clubs.)
    - Societies-Quadrants. Men's dormitories honor society. (Box 51)
    - Societies-Research Club of Michigan University. (Box 51)
    - Societies-Zeta Phi Eta. (Box 51)
      (Includes also Portia (original local branch), Readers' Theatre.)
    - Societies-Science. (Box 51)
      (see also: Societies-Sigma Xi; Societies-Association of University of Michigan Scientists;-various departments and schools.)
    - Societies-Scroll (sorority senior women's honorary). (Box 51)
    - Societies-Senior Society (unaffiliated senior women's honorary) (Box 51)
    - Societies-Sigma Alpha Iota. Professional Music Sorority. (Box 51)
    - Societies-Sigma Rho Tau. Engineering Speech Society. (Box 51)
    - Societies-Sigma Xi. (Box 51)
    - Societies-Speech.
      (see: Societies-Debating and Oratorical. Societies-)
    - Sphinx (junior men's honor society). (Box 51)
    - Societies-Student Bar Association. (Box 51)
      (see also: Law School-Dances (for Chancellor's Court Dance sponsored by the S.B.A.))
    - Societies-Tau Beta Pi. (national engineering fraternity). (Box 51)
    - Societies-Tolstoy League. (Box 51)
    - Societies-Triangles (sophomore engineering honorary). (Box 51)
    - Societies-Veterans.
      (see: Veterans-Societies.)
    - Societies-Vulcans (senior men's engineering honorary). (Box 51)
    - Societies-Women. (Box 51)
      (Includes Quadrantic Club, Women's Research Club, Graduate Women's Club, Kappa Beta Rho, Underwriters, Alpha Gamma Sigma. see also: Societies-Michigan Dames; Societies-Independents (for Suomynona Club).)
    - Societies-Wyvern (junior women's honorary). (Box 51)
    - Sororities (professional).
      (see: Professional Sororities.)
    - Sophomore Traditions.
      (see: Traditions.)
    - Society for American Archaeology.
      (see: Anthropology, Dept.. of Society for Industrial Lawyers. see: Societies-Law School.)
    - Society for Peaceful Alternatives.
    - Society for the Advancement of Management.
    - Society of Automotive Engineers.
    - Society of Friends.
    - Society of Indian Chemical Engineers.
      (see: Societies-Chemistry)
    - Sociology, Dept. of. (Box 51)
      (see also: Institute of Public and Social Admin.; Population Studies)
    - Soil Conservation Society of America
      (see: Natural Resources.)
    - Soldier Choir. pee: Glee Clubs.
    - Solid-State Physics Laboratory.
    - Solstis (experimental secondary school) (Box 51)
    - Songs.
      (see: Music.)
    - Soph Show. (formerly Sophomore Cabaret). (Box 51)
    - Sophomore Cabaret. (1956 became Soph Show). (Box 51)
    - Sophomore prom. (Box 51)
    - Sophomore Satire.
      (see: Freshmen-Frosh Weekend.)
    - Special Publications Serv.
      (see: University Relations Service.)
    - Sororities (Social)
      (see also: Fraternities-FBA; Race Problems.)
      - General (Box 51)
      - Alphabetical
        - A (Box 51)
        - B --C (Box 51)
        - D (Box 51)
        - E-J (Box 51)
        - K-0 (Box 51)
        - P-R (Box 51)
        - S-Z (Box 51)
    - Sororities (Panhellenic List of Sororities, 1957)
      (Alpha Chi Omega; Alpha Delta Pi; Alpha Epsilon Phi; Alpha Gamma Delta; Alpha Omicron Pi; Alpha Phi; Alpha Xi Delta; Chi Omega; Collegiate Sororsis; Delta Delta Delta; Delta Gamma; Delta Phi Epsilon; Gamma Phi Beta; Kappa Alpha Theta Kappa Delta; Kappa Kappa Gamma; Phi Mu; Pi Beta Phi; Sigma Delta Tau; Sigma Kappa; Zeta Tau Alpha)
    - Sororities. Charities.
      (see: Sororities; Sororities-Panhellenic; Sororities-Rushing (Help Week).)
    - Sororities-Delta Gamma (Box 51)
    - Sororities-Delta Zeta (Box 51)
    - Sororities-'Discrimination" Clauses. (i.e. Binding or required recommendations)
      (see: Sororities-Panhellenic.)
    - Sororities. Panhellenic.
      (Includes Varsity Show, Ball, Workshop, scholarship, housing, Pan-Helpers, parade, sorority-dorm dinner, exchanges, newspaper. see also: Fraternities-IFC; Fraternities-Greek Week.)
      - 1920-1939 (Box 51)
      - 1940-1951 (Box 51)
      - 1952-1955 (Box 51)
      - 1956 (Box 51)
    - Sororities. Rushing.
      (see also: Fraternities-Rushing)
      - 1928-1948 (Box 51)
      - 1949-1960 (Box 51)
      - 1961 (Box 51)
    - Sororities. Sigma Kappa. (Box 51)
    - South American Expeditions. Lee: Expeditions-South and Central America
    - South East Asia.
      (see: Far Eastern Studies. Plans for South East Asian delegation see: Student Government (1957-))
    - Southern Asian Studies, Center for.
      (see: Far Eastern Studies. Southerners Club. see: Societies-Q-Z.)
    - Space Physics Laboratory.
    - Space Research.
      (see also: Engineering, College of Aeronautical and Astronautical; Alumni-Astronauts)
    - Spanish Civil War.
      (see: Campus Events, 1936-7;)
    - Foreign Visitors.
    - Spanish Club.
    - Spanish Lang. and Lit.
      (see: Romance Lang. and Lit., Dept. of Speaker's ban. see references under-Free Speech.)
    - Speakers Bureau (Organized by Office of Student Organizations)., 1967
      (see: Student Affairs, Office of.)
    - Statistical Research Laboratory (Est. June 21, 1946).
      (see: Statistics, Dept. of)
    - Spectroscopy Laboratory.
      (see: Engineering, College of-Chemical and Electrical.)
    - Speech Clinic.
      (see: Institute for Human Adjustment-Speech Clinic.)
    - Speech, Dept. of, 1945-1965; 2 folders (Box 51)
      (see also; .Linguistic Institute; English, Dept. of (for early days only); Speech, Dept. of Institute for Human Adjustment-Speech Clinic (includes Speech Camp; Societies-Debating and Oratorical; For dramatic productions see also: Play Product.-(3 Acts); Dramatics (1 Act, Readers, Theatre, Experimental Playbill, and misc.); Dramatics-Repertory Players (summer session plays).)
    - Speech Dept. summer playbill. (Box 52)
      (see: Dramatics-Repertory Players)
    - Speech Improvement Camp.
    - Speech Research Laboratory.
      (see: Speech, Depart. of. May 13, 1960-changed to communication sciences laboratory and set up as a separate budgetary unit within the Literary College.)
    - Sphinx.
      (see: Societies-Sphinx.)
    - Spoken Language Training, Workshop in.